pornopaul.com 2002-12-09

# Guns

**

Melvista.com Privacy Policy

**

Melvista.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our online visitors. This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices governing the use of information submitted to Guns.com through this web site.

**

The Information We Collect

**

This site contains a section from which you can bid on key words. If you decide to become a registered user, bid on key words, or receive updates from this site, you will be asked to provide us with certain information including, for example, a valid email address and credit card number for billing purposes. **** We collect your contact information so that we can process your order and provide you with the information you requested. Additionally, we collect IP addresses, domain names when provided by visitors and aggregate information on pages visited as well as information volunteered by consumers in interactive elements such as polls. **** The credit card information collected is strictly used for billing purposes. If you have any questions about billing or service, you are welcome to address them by contacting info@melvista.com. Please be aware that our site contains links to other sites and that privacy practices of these other sites may differ from those of Melvista.com. Each site is responsible for its own privacy practices.

**

Information Usage and Sharing

**

Melvista.com values your patronage and respects your right to privacy. Because we are committed to protecting your privacy, personal data relating to an identified or identifiable individual that is submitted to this web page will be collected, processed stored, and disposed of in accordance with applicable U.S. law. However, U.S. law may not provide the degree of protection to personal data, which is available in other countries. The submission of personal data constitutes the User’s acknowledgement that he/she has read and understood this notice, and agrees to its terms. Melvista.com may share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with unaffiliated third parties for marketing or research purposes.

**

Updating your Account/Melvista.com Opt-Out policy

**

We require subscribers holding accounts on our site to permit us to communicate with them regarding their accounts. If you are a subscriber you consent to receiving e-mail from Melvista.com. We also give users the following additional options for removing or updating their information from our database:

You can send email to info@melvista.com

**

Cookies

**

Melvista.com uses cookie technology to increase the ease of use of the web site. When you make selections or set preferences on our site, the site will send a request to your browser to record some of your selections in a "cookie" file. The cookie is a small text file that resides on your hard drive. From time to time, our site will request the cookie from your browser so we can retrieve the stored information and you do not have to repeatedly enter information. Should you choose not to accept these cookies you may not be able to use portions of our site.

Melvista.com never uses cookies to store credit card information, nor is the information we store in the cookie intended to be read by any other web site.

Many browsers allow users to set the preferences to show a warning each time a cookie request is received. You can also set most browsers not to accept cookies at all.

At times, some of the advertisers on our site set cookies when you select their ad banner. We do not receive the data collected by those cookies.

**

Security

**

Melvista.com has security measures in place to safeguard against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. By making your bids and or purchases through our secure server, you are protected by Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") technology, used by most browsers, including Netscape and Microsoft Explorer. **** This technology allows us to utilize advanced encryption in order to protect the information transmitted between your computer and our server. Through encryption, the personal information you enter, including your name and credit card information, is securely dispatched over the Internet.

**

Policy Changes

**

As Melvista.com grows and new features are added or legal requirements change, this privacy policy may be modified. Although all information submitted to Melvista.com is subject to the terms and conditions of this policy and any modifications, you may remove or restrict access to your account by updating your account information at www.Melvista.com. Any changes to the Melvista.com privacy policy will be posted online.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at info@melvista.com
